A Guide to the Records of the Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Campaign Expense Accounts, 1992-2007
Library of Virginia
- I. Political Action Committees (PACs), 2003-2007., Extent: 21 cubic feet (21 boxes). (Box 1-21)
  - International Union of Partner and Allied Trades Legislative Education, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Local 14 International Union of Operating Engineers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Issues Mobilzation PAC (IMPAC), 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Jackson and Reinicke for Council, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - John F. Fick III and Charles McDaniel, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - JP Morgan Chase and Co. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Just PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Kaine Inaugural 2006, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Keeping America's Promise Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Laborers Local 11 PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Land America Financial Group Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Leadership PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Leadership '02 Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Leadership for Virginia's Future, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Leadership for Lynchburg, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Leadership for Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - The Leadership Forum, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Lee County Education Association, PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Lee District Republican Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Libertarian Party of Virginia, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Libertarina Party of Northern Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Loudoun Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Loudoun County Republican Women's Club, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Loudoun Taxpayers Coalition, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Louisa County Republican Committe, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Lt. Governor Inaugural Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Lynchburg Voters League, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - MACPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - M-PAC Political Action Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Madison Project PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Main Street Fund Individual, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Manassas Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Maritime Issues Council, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Steering Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Mason District Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Maximus, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 11)
  - Mayor at Large Referendum Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Bob McDonnell Inaugural Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - MCI Atlantic States PAC, 2003-2007 (1 of 2) (Box 12)
  - MCI Atlantic State PAC, 2003-2007 (2 of 2) (Box 12)
  - McQuire Woods LLP, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mead/Westvaco Corporation Political Participation Program, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Medical Society of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mercantile Bankshares Corporation State PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Merritt Properties LLC Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Metropolitan Washington PAC for Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - MH Golf Classic, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Carpenters PAC Virginia District, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Minority Business Enterprise PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - ModerateGOP.com, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Monticello Business Alliance PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mosby Woods Advocates, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mountain PAC of Educators, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Mountain Vista Governors School Seniors, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - NASW-VA PAC for Candidate Elections, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Association of Health, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Association for Uniformed Services, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Federation of Independent Business, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Public Affairs PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Nationwide Virginia Political Participation Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - National Republican Congressional Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - NEA Fund for Children's Education, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - Neighbors for Herndon, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - New Century Leadership Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - New Dominion PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - New Leadership Virginia Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 12)
  - New River Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - New River Valley Builders, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Newman-Putney PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Next PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - NiSource Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Norfolk Rainbow Coalition, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Norfolk Southern Corporation Good Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Northern Virginia Realtors PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Northern Virginia Democratic Business Council, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - NRA Political Victory Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - NVTC TechPAc, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union Voice of the Electorate, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - One Arlington PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - One Hanover PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - One Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - OPEIU Voice of the Electorate, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Old Dominion Highway PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Oracle Corporation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Ortho PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - Our Neighborhood, 2003-2007 (Box 13)
  - PAC for Affordable Housing of the Peninsula, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PAC for the Battlefield Lodge of the FOP, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PAC for the Association of the Virginia Fraternal Order of Police, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PAC of the Tidewater Builders Association, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Partnership for Peninsula's Future, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Pataki PAC Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Patrick Henry PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Patriots PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Peninsula Progress PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Peninsula Lincoln Day Dinner, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PEPCO PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PFIZER Inc. PAc, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PHILPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Physical Therapy PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Piedmont Defense Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Piedmont Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Piedmont Leadership PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Piedmont Stone Center, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PILLPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Pioneer PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Plumbing and Mechanical Professionals of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Portsmouth Citizens for Tax Fairness, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Portsmouth PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Prince William County Democratic Leadership Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Prince William Police Association, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Print PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Pro Choice PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Professionals PAC (HDR et al), 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Progress Energy Employees Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Progressive Eagle Club, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Propane PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Protect Children Online, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - PsychMED PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Raising Kaine PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
  - Real Estate Issues Mobilization, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Real Nelson PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Realtor PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Realtors PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Reed Smith, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Reform Party of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republican National Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republican Leadership Council, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republican State Leadership Committee-Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republicans for Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republicans for York, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republicans and Independents for Pollard, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republicans of the Commonwealth, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Republican Senate Victory PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Responsible Government PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Responsible Government for Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Revercomb and McConnell for Council, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Apartment Management PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Area Municipal Contractors Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Realtors PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Roanoke City Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Roanoke County Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Roanoke Sheriffs Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Rockbridge Citizens Advisory Council, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Rockbridge Green Party Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Ronald Reagan Club, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Rough Mountain Leadership PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Royal Indemnity Company Voluntary PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Russell County PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - RX Care PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - SOS-Save Our Schools, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Save the Arlington Way, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - School Bonds 2004, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Scott County Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - SCORE PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - SHAV PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Shaw Pittman PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Shenandoah Valley Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Skyline PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Six PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Smithfield Foods, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Smokeless Tobacco Council PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Smyth County Democratic Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Smyth County Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Southern Donkey, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Southern Party of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Southern States Police Benevolent Association PAC Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Southside UniServ PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Southwest United Builders PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Spectrum Healthcare Service Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Spotsylvania County Land Owners, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Spotsylvania Voters to Stop Sprawl, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Sprint Nextel Corporation, 2003-2007 (1 of 5) (Box 16)
  - Sprint Nextel Corporation, 2003-2007 (2 of 5) (Box 16)
  - Sprint Nextel Corporation, 2003-2007 (3 of 5) (Box 16)
  - Sprint Nextel Corporation, 2003-2007 (4 of 5) (Box 16)
  - Sprint Nextel Corporation, 2003-2007 (5 of 5) (Box 16)
  - Stafford County Homeowners Coalition, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - Stafford County Victory PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 16)
  - The St. Paul Traveler Company Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - STAR PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - State Employee Rights Campaign Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Storm Chasers, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Straight Talk America, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Strategic Energy PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Students of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Suffolk PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Sun Trust Responsible Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Support Schools Now, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Supporters for Term Limits, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Target Citizens Multi State Forum, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Tazewell County Democratic Constitutional Officers, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Tazewell Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - TEA PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Tejada-Hynes '07, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Tiger Progress PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - TIMPAC (Governor Kaine's PAC), 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Together for Our Majority PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Truckers PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Tusk and Trunk Club, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Trust Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - United Parcel Service PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - United for Progress PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Universal Leaf Tobacco County Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - United Mine Workers of America UMWA General Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - USINPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Valero Energy Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Valley Leadership Trust, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - VAMA PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - VAMB PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - VAPAC-Independent Mutual Insurance Agents of Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - VAPMACS, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Verizon Good Government Club of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Veterinarians PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 17)
  - Victory 2005, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia 21, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Action Committee for Rural Electrification, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia AgPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Aggregases Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia AIA PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Association of Health Plans PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Association of Mutual Insurance Companies PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Association of Surveyors, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Auto and Truck Dealers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Bankers Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Coalition of Public Employees (COPE), 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Beach Education Association PAC for Education, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Beach Libertarian Party, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Beach Professional Firefighter PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Beach Taxpayers Alliance, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Beer Wholesalers Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Birth PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Cable PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Chamber PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Chiropractic PAC Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Citizens Defense League, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Club for Growth PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Coal Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Coalition of Motorcyclists, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia College Democratic Action Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Committee for Good Government, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Young Democrats, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Counselors Association Challenge Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Credit Union PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Dental PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Dental Hygienist PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Dietetic Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Eagle Forum PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Equine PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - virginia Engineers, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Family Values, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Federation of BPW, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Federation of Chapters, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Fife and Drum, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia First PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Food Dealers Association PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 18)
  - Virginia for Democracy, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Freedom Party, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Friends of Tort Reform, Ind., 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Fund for Good Government, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Gasoline Marketers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Greater Washington Board of Trade PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Gun Owners PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Healthcare Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Highlands Advancement Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Homesteaders, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Horsemen's Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Hospital PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Hospitality and Travel Industry Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independent Living PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independent Power PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Land Title Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Law Enforcement Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia League of Conservation Voters PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Leadership Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Leadership Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Liberty Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Life and Liberty PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Manufactured and Modular Housing Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Metropolitian Circuit Court Clerks Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Mortgage Bankers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Muslim PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Nurses PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Oil and Gas Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Optometric PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Parent PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Partisans Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Pest Control Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Physical Therapy Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Podiatric Medical Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Poultry Federation PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Professional Firefighters, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Progress Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Psychologists for Legislative Action, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Radiology PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Ready Mix Concrete Association, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Real Estate Attorneys League, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - virginia Retailers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Safe PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - virginia Senate Republican Leadership Trust, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Sheriffs Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Sierra Club PAC, 2003-20007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Society for Human Life PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Society of American Institute of Architects, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Society of Anesthesiologists PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Society of Chiropractic PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Society of Health System Pharmacists PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia State AFL-CIO, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia State Farm Agents and Employees PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia State Police Association, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia State UAW PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Taxicab Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Telecommunications Industry Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Transportation Construction Alliance, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Trial Lawyers PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Urban Democracy PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Vines and Wines PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Water Well PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Wine Wholesalers Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Conservative Values, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Life PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Public Safety, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Responsible Government, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Responsible Leadership, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for a Secure Future, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Jerry Kilgore, 2003-2007 (1 of 2) (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Jerry Kilgore, 2003-2007 (2 of 2) (Box 20)
  - Virginians for Transportation Solutions, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - virginians Futures PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Vision Council of America PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Vision for Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voices for Women, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Volunteer PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Vorys Sater Seymour and Gease LLP Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Vote Bipartisan, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Vote Yes for Parks, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters for a Positive Future, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters for Prince William County's Future, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters for Responsible Government, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl-Albemarle, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl-Fredericksburg, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl, King George, 2003-2007 (Box 20)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl-Frederick County, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Voters to Stop Sprawl-Stafford County, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Vulcan PAC, 2003-2007 (1 of 3) (Box 21)
  - Vulcan PAC, 2003-2007 (2 of 3) (Box 21)
  - Vulcan PAC, 2003-2007 (3 of 3) (Box 21)
  - W. Alvin Hudson for Better Government, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wachovia Corporation Good Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wachovia Virginia Employees Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wal-Mart Stores, Inc. PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Washington Balance PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Washington County Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Washington Gas Light Federal PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Washington Gas Light Virginia PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wendy's Arby's Group International, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - WERKPAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wise Education Association PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Brian Wisneff and Sherman Lea for City Council, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Women Building for the Future PAC, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Womens Campaign Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wood Products PAC of Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Write It In!, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Wyeth Good Government Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Yes, Hanover Bonds, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
  - Young Voters PAC Virginia, 2003-2007 (Box 21)
- II. Virginia House of Delegates, 1993-2005., Extent: 6 cubic feet (6 boxes). (Box 22-25, 29-30)
  Series is arranged chronologically and alphabetically therein.
  - Ebert, Paul - 1993 (Box 22)
  - Hull, Robert - 1995 (Box 22)
  - Hull, Robert - 1997 (Box 22)
  - Barlow, Robert - 1999 (Box 22)
  - Barlow, William - 1999 (Box 22)
  - Hull, Robert - 1999 (Box 22)
  - Stephens, Virginia - 1999 (Box 22)
  - Ashworth, Billy - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Baskerville, Viola - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Blevins, Harry - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Burger, Scott - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Crittenden, Flora - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Dance, Rosalyn - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Dickinson, V. Earl - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Havens, Kirk - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Hill, Richard - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Hull, Robert - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Huskey, Jo Ann - 2001 (Box 22)
  - McCarty, Sharon - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Miller, John - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Montgomery, John - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Moss, Thomas - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Nande, John - 2001 (Box 22)
  - Pocalyko, Mike - 2001 (Box 23)
  - Smith, Danny - 2001 (Box 23)
  - Waters, George - 2001 (Box 23)
  - Woodrum, Clifton - 2001 (Box 23)
  - Alexander, Kenneth - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Battle, Sherry - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Calhoun, Mark - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Cline, Benjamin - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Hawn, Carol - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Hugo, Timothy - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Horsey, Linda - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Linkous, Larry - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Nusbaum, William - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Moddo, Joseph - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Shuler, James - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Albo, David - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Almand, James - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Baskerville, Viola - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Bivens, Sharon - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Bowman, Gary - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Bloxom, Robert - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Brickley, David - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Bryant, Alvin - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Christain, Mary - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Clerici, John - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Council, James - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Cox, Kirkland - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Craig, Christopher - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Dillard, James - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Dix, Thomas - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Dixon, T. Hume - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Donahue, Shawn - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Drake, Thelma - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Elrod, Mimi - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Emick, Mark - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Fedbush, Charles - 2003 (Box 23)
  - Forgit, Phillip - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Fulk, Lowell - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Graham, Michael - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Graham, Thomas - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hale, Allen - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hamilton, Phillip - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hoff, Christian - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hull, Robert - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Hurt, Robert - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Raymond - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Kelly, Gary - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Kelly, James - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Lapetina, Troy - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Levy, Levi - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Lewis, Thomas - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Lipscomb, Arthur - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Louderback, Allen - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Mapp, Betsy - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Marrs, Bradley - 2003 (Box 24)
  - McDougle, Ryan - 2003 (Box 24)
  - McGuire, Hunter - 2003 (Box 24)
  - McQuigg, Michele - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Melvin, Kenneth - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Mills, David - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Monell, Nathan - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Moran, Brian - 2003 (Box 24)
  - Morissey, Patricia - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Newbill, Mark - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Nicholson, John - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Orrock, Robert - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Parrish, Harry - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Petersen, John - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Phillips, Clarence - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Pollard, Albert - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Polchrones, Michael - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Potter, Eric - 2003 (Box 25)